CHERRY ROSE S. FIGUERRA

UI/UX DESIGNER

https://cherosefiguerra.github.io/portfolio/

PROFESSIONAL PROFILE

A self-motivated IT professional having 7 years of work experience as Web Designer, UI/UX and Graphics Designer. Bringing the passion for creating a clean, elegant, user-friendly and user-centric designs. Hoping to share my skills, expertise and experience with your team and valuable clients.

SKILLS

Tools

Adobe Photoshop

Adobe Lightroom

Adobe XD

Figma

Sketch

Github

Languages / Frameworks

HTML

CSS

Bootstrap

JavaScript

CREATIVE FIELD

Web Design

User Interface

Mock Up

Prototype

Poster/Flyer

App Design

Branding Logo

Banner Infographic

Wireframes

ACADEMIC BACKGROUND

2011 - 2015

BS Information Technology

Manuel S. Enverga University Foundation Lucena City, Quezon Province

 3rd Year Department Council Secretary

CONTACT



09301251741



cherose.figuerra@gmail.com



https://www.linkedin.com/in/ cherryrosefiguerra/



https://www.behance.net/che1028

JOB EXPERIENCES

MYSERVICEFORCE | Pennsylvania, USA December 2020 - October 2023

UI/UX AND WEB DESIGNER

- Created a mock-ups and visual design for our ERP systems, websites and mobile applications
- Appcues Integrations
- Created a marketing material such as banners sell sheets and logos.

SHIPTEK SOLUTIONS CORP. | San Pedro City, Laguna

January 2019 - April 2019

MOBILE DEVELOPER

- Created a mobile application for android and iOS devices. Familiarity with hybrid mobile development framework like Ionic.
- Basic Integrations

AMERITECH GLOBAL SOLUTIONS INC. Lipa City, Batangas

April 2015 - September 2018

FRONT-END WEB DEVELOPER

- Created a website using HTML, CSS, Bootstrap and JavaScript following client-approved mock-ups and visual design.
- Updates websites content and layout based from the client request.
- Executes full-stack website launches specializing in front-end features, browser manipulation, and cross-browser compatibility.
- Resolved design issues through root cause analysis and performed data cleanups.

GRAPHICS DESIGNER

- Created a mock-ups and visual design for website and mobile applications,
- Created a marketing material such as banners, brochures, flyers, postcards, business cards, menus, sale sheets, t-shirts, calendars, gift certificates, event tickets, company logos.
- Familiarity of image editing tools being able to edit, redesign, crop, resize, or perform adjustments on an image.
- Ability to absorb and apply constructive criticism from peers and clients.

VIDEO EDITOR

 Created a simple animation using adobe flash and video editing using adobe premiere.

FRONT-END MOBILE DEVELOPER

- Created a mobile application layout, familiarity with software like Android studio and Visual Studio Code.
- · Updates content and layout based from the client request.